Guide to the George Adams Shuford Papers, 1952-1959
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series
  - Taxation:
    - H.R. 3316. Simpson Bill. An amendment to Sec. 120 of Internal Revenue Code (Box 77)
    - H.R. 3589 and H.R. 3468. Tax on Non-Profit Groups (Box 77)
    - H.R. 4259. One yr. extension excise tax-$20.00 credit individual income. Ways and Means Com. (Box 77)
    - H.R. 5180. Mason Bill (Box 77)
    - H.R. 6409 (Box 77)
    - H.R. 8300. Tax Bill (Box 77)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 77)
    - Tax Exemption (Box 77)
    - Tax Revision Bill (Box 77)
  - Telegraph Account:
    - 1953 (Box 77)
    - 1954 (Box 77)
    - 1955 (Box 77)
    - 1956 (Box 77)
    - 1957 (Box 77)
  - Telephone Account:
    - 1953 (Box 77)
    - 1954 (Box 77)
    - 1955 (Box 77)
    - 1956 (Box 77)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 77)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority: (Box 78)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 78)
    - 1955 (Box 78)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 78)
    - Dixon-Yates Matter (Box 78)
    - Handbook on TVA (Box 78)
    - S. 2373. Amend TVA Act of1933 (Box 78)
    - Self-financing (Box 78)
    - Tax Equivalents Paid by TVA. 1953 (Box 78)
    - Water Reservoir System (Box 78)
  - Territories:
    - Alaska. Fairbanks (Box 78)
    - Statehood. Alaska and Hawaii. 1953-1954 (Box 78)
    - Statehood on Alaska and Hawaii. 1955-1956 (Box 78)
    - Statehood. Alaska and Hawaii. 1957-1958 (Box 79)
  - Territories Subcommittee:
    - General Correspondence. 1955-1956 (Box 79)
    - General.1957 (Box 79)
    - Legislation.1956 (Box 79)
    - Legislation.1957 (Box 79)
  - Tobacco:
    - 1953-1954 (Box 79)
    - Burley (Box 79)
    - Burley. Graduated Excise Tax Hearings H.R. 4829. To increase the national marketing quota for burley tobacco by 10 per centum (Box 79)
    - General. 1957-1958 (Box 79)
    - Processed. May 1,2,3,1956 (Box 79)
  - Transylvania County. General (Box 80)
  - Department of Treasury. 1955 (Box 80)
  - Trinity River:
    - Development (Box 80)
    - Division. Central Valley Project (Box 80)
    - H.R. 6997and H.R. 7407 (Box 80)
  - Trips of Mr. Shuford
    - 1953 (Box 80)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 80)
    - 1957 (Box 80)
  - Tungsten. H.R. 2824. Aspinall Bill on Tungsten (Box 80)
  - Unagusta Furniture Company (Box 81)
  - Un-American Activities. Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 81)
  - Veterans:
    - 1953 (Box 81)
    - Administration.1958 (Box 81)
    - Affairs.1958 (Box 81)
    - Affairs. Copies of Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 81)
    - Affairs Committee. Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 81)
    - Affairs Committee. General. 1955-1956 (Box 81)
    - Affairs Committee. General.1957 (Box 81)
    - Hospital Subcommittee. General. 1957-1958 (Box 82)
    - Hospital Subcommittee. Investigation. Vet. Adm. medical program (Box 82)
    - Hospital Subcommittee. Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 82)
    - Housing Subcommittee. 1955-1956 (Box 82)
    - Housing Subcommittee.1957 (Box 82)
    - Institutional. On-Farm Training (Box 82)
    - Insurance Subcommittee (Box 82)
    - Laundries and other activities in Vets. Hospitals (Box 82)
    - Legislation. 1953-1954 (Box 82)
    - Legislation.1955 (Box 82)
    - Legislation.1956 (Box 83)
    - Legislation.1957 (Box 83)
    - Legislation.1958 (Box 83)
    - Legislation. Select Committee on Survivors Benefits 1955-1956 (Box 83)
    - H.R. 53. H.R. 71. H.R. 72. Re: Special Sub-committee (Box 84)
    - H.R. 72 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 73 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1261. To Amend Veterans Regulation No. 2(a) to establish an effective date of awards of pension in the case of certain veterans **** pulmonary tuberculosis (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1262. To authorize and direct the Administrator of Veterans Affairs to accept certain land in Buncombe Co., N.C., for cemetery purposes (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1263. To amend title III of the Servicemen's Readjustment Act to remove certain impediments to the processing of applications for V.A. direct loans. etc. (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1264. To provide that certain veterans suffering from active p.t. shall be deemed to be permanently and totally for pension purposes while they are hospitalized (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2573 and H.R. 2574. Spanish Amer. War Vets. (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2741. To direct the administrator of Vets. affairs to convey certain lands to the Hermann (Box 85)
    - Hosp. Estate. Houston, Tex. (Box 85)
    - H.R. 4602. Mr. Teague's Bill to encourage new residential construction for veterans housing in rural areas and small cities. (Box 85)
    - H.R. 4666. To encourage new residential const. for vet's housing by raising the maximum amt. from $10,000 to $12,500. etc. (Box 85)
    - H.R. 4625. To amend Sec. 605 of Natl. Service Inc. Act to provide for investment of 20% of the natl. service ins. fund in making loans etc. (Box 85)
    - H.R. 5116. To amend Servicemen's Readjustment Act of1944,so as to authorize loans for farm housing to be guaranteed or insured under the same (Box 85)
    - H.R. 5727. A bill to amend the Servicemen's Readjustment Act of1944to extend the authority of the V.A. to make direct loans (Box 85)
    - H.R. 7886 (Box 85)
    - H.R. 7886 (Box 85)
    - H.R. 9020 (Box 86)
    - H.R. 9282. Amend title III of the Servicemen's Readjustment Act of1944,as amended and for other purposes (Box 86)
    - H.R. 9700. A bill to consolidate into one act all of the laws administered by the V.A. and for other purposes (Box 86)
    - H.R. 10166. A bill to extend and liberalize the direct home loan program for veterans (Box 86)
    - H.R. 10238 (Box 86)
    - H.R. 10477. and H.R. 10478. Special Sub-committee (Box 86)
    - V.A. Loans.1956 (Box 86)
    - V.A. Loans.1957 (Box 86)
    - V.A. Loans.1958 (Box 86)
  - Vivisection (Box 87)
  - Voting Record (Box 87)
  - Water Control:
    - Information. S. 2549 (Box 87)
    - Pollution. 1956 (Box 87)
    - Pollution. 1956 (Box 87)
    - Stream Pollution. H.R. 234 (Box 87)
  - Ways and Means:
    - Copies of Bills. 1954-1956 (Box 87)
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 87)
    - Legislation.1956 (Box 88)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 88)
    - Legislation.1958 (Box 89)
  - Wheland Company (Box 89)
- Oversize Folder
  - The Capitol in Story and Pictures (84th Congress, 1st Session, House Document No. 232) (Opaperfolder 1)
  - The Capitol, A Pictorial Story of the Capitol in General and the House Representatives in Particular (85th Congress, 2nd Session, House Document No. 412) (Opaperfolder 1)